mypage5.com 2012-05-30

# MyPage 5 : meet new friends as you network, share photos, create blogs, share videos, upload music, make new friends, revenue sharing, social networking website uk, dating uk, videos uk

**Personal Information Collected Via Technology**

As you navigate the website, certain information may also be passively collected and stored on our server logs, including your Internet protocol address, browser type, and operating system. We also use Cookies and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and viewed, or on which of the advertisements displayed on the Website you clicked. This type of information is collected to make our services and solutions more useful to you and to tailor the MYPAGE5.COM community experience to meet your special interests and needs.

If you search the MYPAGE5.COM community by using a toolbar that MYPAGE5.COM or a third party provides, we may collect Anonymous Information about you automatically, but we will not collect Personal Information.

An “Internet Protocol Address” or “IP Address” is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the internet. In some cases your IP Address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer internet access provider, your IP Address probably varies from session to session. We track your IP Address when you login to the Website.

“Cookies” are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing a website. MYPAGE5.COM may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on the website. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following your Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable Cookies, some areas of the website may not work properly.

Other third parties may place advertisements and cookies on web pages within the MYPAGE5.COM network. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the MYPAGE5.COM service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the MYPAGE5.COM Newsletter, that are considered part of your MYPAGE5.COM account. If you would like to log out of certain messages, log into MYPAGE5.COM and go to your account settings by clicking the account link in the top right hand corner. On that page you can edit your preferences. If you would like to delete your account, log into MYPAGE5.COM, go to your account settings page by clicking the account link in the top right hand corner. On that page, right below the email address field you will see a link to cancel your account.

**Confidentiality and Security**

In regards to employees and third-parties we check access to personal information about you if we reasonably believe need access to such information so as to provide you with necessary products or services or in order for them to carry out their job effectively.

We have physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you and your MYPAGE5.COM account information is protected by a password that you select. MYPAGE5.COM uses industry standard SSL encryption in certain areas of the website to protect data transmissions.

However, no company, including MYPAGE5.COM, can fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information.

**Other Sites**

It is not within our power to monitor or control outside websites and their content, we are not responsible for them. Any link that we provide to you via our network to other websites is solely for your personal convenience and is not an indication of our support for such websites and their content. Thus please be advised that the terms and conditions of our Privacy Policy apply to our network alone and not websites outside of our network.

**Regarding Children**

In regards to visitor whom are under the age of 16 years, we do not intentionally gather Personal Information in reference to them.

**Contact Us**

If you have any queries regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Mypage5.com Ltd

37 Stanmore Hill, Stanmore,

Middlesex HA7 3DS, United Kingdom.

_Email:privacy@mypage5.com._

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Notification will be corresponded to you in the event of MYPAGE5.COM updating its Privacy Policy which can affect the way in which your Personal Information is handled. In such a case notification will be forwarded to you mainly through the email address you provided in your MYPAGE5.COM account or at times we may post prominent notices on our homepage. If following you have any objections to any modifications made to the Privacy Policy you must STOP using our website. Whereby you continue to use our website this will be taken as receipt of you’re in agreement to such changes and thus making you legally bound by the terms and conditions of any alterations made.
